>> Jem Young: 确保软件安全的一种方法，或者
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So one way of
keeping your software secure, or
确保您的电脑安全，防止这一天的发生。
keeping your computer secure,
is preventing these zero days.
因此，当一个漏洞发生时，您希望使您的软件保持最新状态。
So the minute an exploit comes out,
you want to keep your software up to date.
我们可以用一个叫做 " 无人照管升级" 的项目来完成这个过程。
And we can do this with a program
called Unattended Upgrades.
它所做的是自动升级软件以进行安全性或次要修订。
What it does is it automatically upgrades
your software for security or minor fixes.
现在让我们把它安装在我们的电脑上。
So let's go ahead and
install that now on our computer.
那就这样吧
So sudo.
适当安装无人照管升级。
apt install unattended-upgrades.
>> Jem Young: 执行
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Do that
在这里
here.
一般的 Ubuntu 分发版
And generally with modern
Ubuntu distributions,
已经安装了因为他们想帮你
it's already installed because
they're trying to help you out.
每个版本的 Ubuntu 变得更好，更方便用户。
Every version of Ubuntu gets a little bit
better, a little bit more user friendly.
让我们看看 conf 文件吧
And let's just check on the conf file.
我们今天不会修改它，但很高兴知道这些 conf 文件存在。
We're not gonna modify it today, but it's
good to know that these conf files exist.
所以我要少说
So I'm gonna say less,
>> Jem Young: /etc/ apt， apt.conf.d 和
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: /etc/ apt, apt.conf.d, and
我们将进行 50 个无人值守的升级
we'll go with 50 unattended upgrades.
>> Jem Young: 对于 etc/APT/APT.conf./unattendeupgradand
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: For an
etc/APT/APT.conf.d/unattendedupgrades and
这些只是程序的配置文件，对于
these are just configuration files for
the programs, for
应用程序及其在后台运行的特定实例。
apps and in this particular
instance it runs in the background.
所以它所做的就是因为他们的所有东西都被注释掉了
So what it does is because most of
their everything's commented out,
除了保安外
other than the security.
分布在主要分布上
And distribution for
the main distribution,
这通常不会发生
which usually doesn't happen.
通常不会对 LTS 版本进行重大的推送。
There's not usually a major
push on LTS version.
我不知道 ESM 是什么但我觉得还行
And I don't know what ESM is,
but I think it's okay.
但我们最想要的就是安全升级。
But the main one we want
is the security upgrades.
所以每次在 Ubuntu 发现一个漏洞和漏洞
So every time there's a bug and
exploit discovered in Ubuntu,
您的计算机会自动为您进行最新的更改。
your computer is automatically going
to pull in the latest changes for you.
这是很有帮助的。
This is really helpful.
当我第一次开始的时候，这并不存在。
When I first started out,
this didn't really exist.
因此我必须运行一个定时作业，它是一个每天运行的作业，或者
So I had to run a cron job which is
a job that runs on a daily cycle or
不管我建立了什么东西都能自动安装这些东西
whatever I established it to be and
automatically install these things but
没有意外的升级它会为你带来的
with unintended upgrades,
it does it for you.
那就是，这只是一个非常好的特征，如果它是
And that's, that's just a a really nice
feature that we should all enable if it's
尚未在系统中启用。
not already enabled in your system.
始终确保您的系统具有保持最新的方式。
Always make sure your system has
a way of staying up to date.
Windows Update ，我想 Windows 10，他们那天放了零一天，
Windows Update, I think Windows 10,
they had a zero day release the other day,
是从视频或者类似的东西
it was from a video drive or
something like that.
因此，如果您可以，请始终使您的软件保持最新状态。
So again, always keep your
software up to date if you can.
但不一定要跳最新版本的东西。
But don't necessarily jump on
the latest version of something.
但是请保持最新的补丁和修订。
But stay on the latest patches and fixes.
嗯。
Yes.
>> 演讲者 2: 因此，一旦您运行此安装程序，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So to clarify,
once you run this installer,
这将会是自动驾驶的自动驾驶
that's going to essentially be
an autopilot and it will automatically
删除自动安装程序或自动升级程序 >> Jem Young: 是。
delete auto installer or auto upgrader
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes.
>> 演讲者 2: 这个时间表的频率是多少 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: And
what's the frequency of that schedule?
> > Jem Young: 我不知道，我觉得它可能每天都在检查。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: I don't know,
I think it checks probably daily.
只是检查一下附买回来说这事有什么最新进展吗
It just checks the apt repo and
says is there an update to this?
如果是，请将其拉出并安装。
If so, pull it in and install it.
>> 扬声器 2: 因此，理论上，您仍然容易受到零天的影响。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So theoretically you
would still be vulnerable to zero days.
>> Jem Young: 是。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes.
所以他们被称为零日
Which is why they're called a zero day.
如果他们被称为一天
If they were called a one day,
足够给你足够的时间来解决这个问题
that would be enough to give
you enough time to fix it.
如果是零，你的系统在运行，那么还没拍
If it's a zero day and your system is
running, then it's not patched yet
因为制造商根本就不知道
because the manufacturer
doesn't even know about it.
因此它的零部分。
Hence the zero part of it.